Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Legislative Papers, 1920-1953 (Box 471-870)
  - Negroes in Army and Navy, 1945 (Box 726)
    - Reports, Labor Committee-Joint Committee, 1947-1949
    - Republican campaign and arguments, 1942, (2 folders)
    - Republican National Committee
      - General
        - 1942
        - 1942-1950, (3 folders) (Box 785)
      - Chicago, 1942
    - Republican Party, Willkieism, 1940-1943 (Box 786)
    - Republican policies, 1938-1941
    - Republican policy and propaganda, 1945-1949
    - Republican principles, 1950, (6 folders) (Box 787)
    - Retaliation, 1949 (Box 788)
    - Rubber, 1947-1950, (2 folders)
    - Rubber and gasoline, 1943
    - Rural Electrification Authority, 1943-1945
    - Russia, 1945-1948
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 789)
      - 1941-1947, (4 folders)
      - 1948-1953, (2 folders) (Box 790)
    - Savings, bonds and compulsory proposals, 1942-1943
    - School construction, 1949, (2 folders)
    - School lunch program, 1944-1946
    - Scientific Foundation, 1949 (Box 791)
    - Scientific research, 1947
    - Secondary boycotts, 1949
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1938-1946
    - Selective service
      - General
        - 1941, 1942, (3 folders)
        - 1945 (Box 792)
      - Classification S. 2510, 1942, (3 folders)
    - Senate chamber reconstruction, 1945-1951, (2 folders) (Box 793)
    - Senate contests, 1947, (2 folders)
    - Senate investigation, 1953
    - Senate organization, 1953, (2 folders)
    - Senate rules, 1949-1953, (2 folders) (Box 794)
    - Silver, 1934-1946, (2 folders)
    - Small business (Box 795)
      - General, 1942-1950, (4 folders)
      - Automobiles and tires, 1942-1944, (3 folders) (Box 796)
      - Bills, 1947
      - Civilian supply, 1943, (2 folders)
    - Small business loan plan, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 797)
    - Senate bill #1122, 1943
    - Small War Plants Corp., 1943-1944
    - Social Protection Bill, S. 1779, 1946
    - Social security
      - General
        - 1938-1939
        - 1945-1950, (4 folders) (Box 798, Box 799, Box 800)
        - 1950-1953, (3 folders) (Box 801)
      - Amendments, 1948-1951
      - Bill H.R. 6000, 1950
      - Federalization, 1941-1942, (3 folders) (Box 802)
      - Legislation
        - 1948-1950, (5 folders)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 803)
      - Medical care, 1939-1946, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1949, (4 folders) (Box 804)
      - National Association of Life Underwriters, 1950 (Box 805)
      - National health, Marjorie Shearon, 1945-1949, (4 folders)
      - Old age pensions, 1943-1949 (Box 806)
      - Puerto Rico, 1950
      - Status quo resolution, 1948
      - Unemployment compensation, 1945-1950, (3 folders)
    - Soldier voting
      - 1943-1944
      - 1944-1945 (Box 807)
    - South American spending, 1943-1944, (2 folders)
    - Southwestern Power Administration, 1951
    - Speech material
      - 1948-1949
      - 1949 (Box 808)
    - Speeches and memoranda, 1945
    - Spend-Lend
      - General
        - 1938-1939, (3 folders)
        - 1939-1940 (Box 809)
      - Barkley Act (S. 2759), 1939
      - For the Floor, 1939
    - Stassen, Harold E., 1950
    - Stabilization Fund, 1939-1940
    - State Department propaganda, exchange of students, 1946-1947
    - State election laws, 1940 (Box 810)
    - States rights, 1947
    - Statistics
      - 1948-1950
      - Business profits, 1942-1948, (3 folders)
      - Commodity prices, 1947-1950
    - Steel (Box 811)
      - General, 1948-1953
      - Case, 1950, (3 folders)
      - Dispute, 1952
      - Hearings, basic price and financial data, 1948 (Box 812)
    - Steering Committee
      - General
        - 1945-1949, (3 folders)
        - 1949, (2 folders) (Box 813)
      - Republican
        - 1944-1945, (4 folders)
        - 1945, (2 folders) (Box 814)
    - Steam pollution
      - 1938-1947, (2 folders)
      - 1947 (Box 815)
    - Subsidies, 1943-1944, (2 folders)
    - Sugar, 1946-1947
    - Supreme Court Bill, 1937-1938
    - Surplus property, 1944, (2 folders) (Box 816)
    - Surplus Property Bill, 1944, (3 folders)
      - Disposal
        - 1943-1945
        - 1945 (Box 817)
    - Surveys and statistics, 1939-1941, (2 folders)
    - Taft Bill (S. 1275), 1939
    - Taft bills and amendments, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 818)
    - Taft-Hartley Act
      - General
        - 1952-1953, (3 folders)
        - 1953 (Box 819)
      - Bill, 1952-1953, (4 folders)
      - Clippings, 1950-1953, (3 folders) (Box 820)
      - Commerce Department, 1953, (2 folders)
      - Communists, 1953 (Box 821)
      - Hearings, 1953, (2 folders)
      - Labor Committee information, 1953
      - Law, 1949
      - Law and American Federation of Labor, 1949-1953
    - Taft original amendments, 1949 (Box 822)
    - Taft on railroad strike, 1946
    - Taft speeches and material
      - 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - 1950 (Box 823)
    - Tariff, 1949, (2 folders)
      - Trade agreements, 1948
      - Trade farm price support, 1949, (1 folder) (Box 824)
    - Taxes
      - General
        - 1942-1950, (3 folders)
        - 1950-1951, (2 folders) (Box 825)
      - Bills
        - 1943, 1950, (3 folders)
        - 1950-1951, (5 folders) (Box 826)
        - 1951, (2 folders) (Box 827)
      - Corporation burden, 1942
      - Income distribution, 1942
      - Conference, 1944 (Box 828)
      - Excise
        - 1951, (3 folders)
        - 1951, (3 folders) (Box 829)
      - Excise profits, 1951, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 830)
      - Measures and fiscal policy, 1943, (2 folders) (Box 831)
      - Mutual, 1942, (2 folders)
      - Proposed policy, 1944
      - Reduction Bill, 1947 (Box 832)
      - Simplification Bill, 1944
      - Taxation
        - General
          - 1938-1939, (2 folders)
          - 1940-1951, (4 folders) (Box 833, Box 834, Box 835)
        - Budget, 1945 (Box 836)
        - Excise taxes, 1947-1950
        - Expenditure policy, 1950-1951
        - Joint Committee study, 1945
        - Life insurance companies, 1950
        - Lincoln Electrical Co., 1938-1953 (Box 837)
        - Plans, Coops, exemptions, 1945-1951, (2 folders)
        - Powers of appointment, 1950
        - Retirement pay and pensions, undated
        - Statistics, 1943-1945
    - Taxes on farm cooperatives, 1951
    - Termination of war powers, 1946-1947, (3 folders) (Box 838)
    - Tidelands
      - 1947
      - 1948-1953, (4 folders) (Box 839)
      - 1953, (2 folders) (Box 840)
      - Debate, 1952
      - Oil case, 1953
    - Townsend Plan, 1939-1941
    - Trade not aid, 1953
    - Training program, 1940-1941, (2 folders) (Box 841)
    - Treaties
      - Nominations and miscellaneous presidential power, 1944-1946
      - S. J. Res. 102, 1952
    - Truman, Harry S., 1944
    - Tyler Kent Case, 1945
    - Un-American Activities, Mundt Bill, 1945
    - Unemployment compensation
      - General, 1946, (1 folder) (Box 842)
      - Emergency Legislation, 1945, (2 folders)
    - Unification of the armed forces, 1946-1947
    - United Medical Administration, 1950
    - United Nations (Box 843)
      - Criminal tribunal, 1952, (4 folders)
      - Powers of delegates, 1945-1952
      - Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1945-1952
    - United States Information Service, 1939 (Box 844)
    - United States State International Army in Europe, 1951
    - Universal Military Training, 1949-1950
    - Valley authorities, 1949
    - Veterans
      - General
        - 1939, 1949-1951, (2 folders)
        - 1940-1952
      - “A” miscellaneous
      - “B-C” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 845)
      - “C-E” miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 846)
      - Education Legislation S. 2596, 1949, (2 folders)
      - “F-H” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 847)
      - “H” miscellaneous (Box 848)
      - Hospitals, 1945-1949
      - “J-K” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 849)
      - Medical, 1951-1953
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 850)
      - “N-P” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “P” miscellaneous (Box 851)
      - Postwar
        - Education, 1943-1944
        - Miscellaneous, 1945-1946
      - Preference, 1940
      - “O-R” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “S” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 852)
      - Seller, Peter W., (2 folders)
      - “T” miscellaneous (Box 853)
      - Tarranova, Mike
      - “U-Z” miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Virgin Islands, 1944-1949 (Box 854)
    - Vocational Education, 1944-1945
    - Vocational Rehabilitation, S. 2714, 1942-1944, (3 folders)
    - Voice of America, 1947-1948 (Box 855)
    - Votes, 1939-1949, (2 folders)
    - Voting record, 1939-1945, (2 folders)
    - Wage Hour Act, Walsh-Healey, 1939 (Box 856)
    - Wage Hour Law
      - 1938-1939
      - 1939-1946, (5 folders) (Box 857)
      - 1946, (2 folders) (Box 858)
    - Wage salary control
      - General, 1942-1944
      - Disney Amendment, 1943
    - Wagner Health Bill, 1939, (2 folders) (Box 859)
    - Wallace, Henry, A., 1946
      - Confirmation, 1945, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 860)
    - Walter Logan Bill, 1940
    - War, 1941
    - War
      - Antiwar agreements
        - 1941, (2 folders)
        - 1941 (Box 861)
      - Balkan intrigue, 1941
      - Civilian liability, S. 2412, 1942
      - Conduct before and after, 1941-1942
      - Crimes trials, Nuernberg, 1946-1948 (Box 862)
      - Damage insurance, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
      - Freedom of the seas, foreign policy, 1941
      - Lend-Lease Bill
        - General, 1941
        - Amendments, hearings, 1941 (Box 863)
      - Peace, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
      - Plants, disposal of, 1945
      - Powers Act, 1942, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 864)
      - Production board and organizations, 1939-1942
      - Production organization operations, 1942
      - Republican reorganization, Wendell Willkie
        - 1940-1941, (2 folders)
        - 1942 (Box 865)
      - Resources Administration, 1940, (2 folders)
      - Responsibility, 1941-1942
      - Roosevelt, Franklin D., speeches, and Taft, 1940-1941
      - Soldier vote, 1943-1944 (Box 866)
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Voting Bill, 1943-1944
      - Speeches (Box 867)
        - Foreign policy and coverage, 1941
        - Peace, 1941, (3 folders)
    - Willkie, Wendell, 1941 (Box 868)
      - Tax Bill, 1942
      - Time, daylight saving time, 1945
    - Watron, Joseph, 1950
    - Welfare funds, 1949
    - Williams, Aubrey W., 1945
    - Willkie, Wendell, 1939-1940 (Box 869)
    - Wilson, Charles E., 1953
    - Wool, 1946-1947, (2 folders)
    - Work Bill, 1945
    - Work Projects Administration, S. 1265, 1939, (2 folders) (Box 870)
    - Work Projects Administration
      - Puerto Rico and Virgin Islands, 1943
    - Yalta Resolution, 1953
    - Young, Joseph, 1949
    - Yugoslavia, undated
- Subject File, 1946-1953 (Box 871-1284)
  Letters received and sent, memoranda, notes, research material, printed matter, and publications by Taft.
  Arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereunder by type of material or name of person, organization, or subject.
  - 1946 (Box 871)
    - Advertising
    - Agriculture
    - Airports
    - Alaska
    - Appointments
      - Executive
    - Appropriations
    - Army
    - Articles
    - Autograph
    - Beaver-Mahoning Canal
    - Bureaucracy
    - Books and booklets
    - Campaign expenditures (Box 872)
    - China
    - Cincinnati, Ohio
    - Civil Aeronautics Administration
    - Civil service
    - Civilian Production Administration
    - Committees
    - Communists
    - Compulsory military training
    - Conscientious objections
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Record
    - Contracts
    - Cooperatives
    - Course in Senate
    - Currency
    - Demobilization
    - Discharge
    - District of Columbia
    - Draft
    - Education
    - Employment
    - Engagements, (5 folders) (Box 873)
    - Equal rights (Box 874)
    - Exports
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee
    - Finland
    - Fisheries
    - Flood
    - Flour
    - Foreign policy
    - Full employment bill
    - Furlough
    - Gallery passes
    - Germany
    - Graves
    - Great Britain
    - Great Lakes Fishing Treaty
    - Greece
    - Hawaii
    - Health
    - Highways
    - Hospitals
    - House of Representatives, H.R. nos. 1000-5999
    - House joint resolutions (Box 875)
    - Housing
    - Immigration
    - Inflation
    - Internal Revenue Service
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations, declined, (3 folders)
    - Italy
    - Jews (Box 876)
    - Kent, Tyler
    - Labor, (2 folders)
    - Leprosy
    - Lists
    - Loan
    - Martin, I. Jack
    - McAdams, William
    - Meade Committee
    - Meat
    - Membership
    - Merchant marines
    - Metals and minerals
    - Milk
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 877)
    - Monetary
    - National Labor Relations Board
    - Navy
    - Negroes
    - Nuremberg trials
    - Office details
    - Office of Price Administration
      - General
      - Act, (2 folders) (Box 878)
    - Ohio state matters
    - Oil
    - Palestine
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Pensions
    - Peru
    - Philippines
    - Poland
    - Political
      - General
      - Action Committee (Box 879)
    - Republicans, (2 folders)
    - Poll tax
    - Positions
    - Post Office
    - Presidency
    - Promotions
    - Private bills (Box 880)
    - Propaganda
    - Public works
    - Publications
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio
    - Railroad retirement
    - Reciprocal trade agreements
    - Recommendations
    - Red Cross
    - Renegotiations
    - Reorganization
    - Reservations
    - Rivers and Harbors
    - Rubber
    - Rural Electric Cooperative
    - Russia
    - St. Lawrence waterway
    - Salaries
    - San Francisco Conference
    - Selective service, (2 folders)
    - Selvage, James P.
    - Senate bills (Box 881)
    - Senators
    - Social Security
    - Sokolsky, George
    - Solid Fuel Administration
    - South America
    - Spain
    - Speakers
    - Speeches
    - Statements
    - State Department
    - Steering committee
    - Strikes
    - Subsidies
    - Sugar
    - Supreme Court
    - Taft, personal friends
    - Tax
    - Transfer
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - Unemployment compensation (Box 882)
    - UNRRA
    - United Nations
    - United States Employment Service
    - Veterans
    - Veterans hospitals
    - Vivisection of animals
    - Voting
    - Wagner-Murray Bill
    - War Department
    - War Damage Insurance
    - War
      - Labor Board
      - Material, disposal of
      - Plants
    - Water
    - Wheat
    - Woiwode, Carl H.
    - Wool
    - Yale
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1947 (Box 883)
    - Agriculture
    - Aid to Europe
    - Appointments
      - Executive
      - Lilienthal, David E., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 884)
    - Appropriations
    - Armed service
    - Articles and statements, (2 folders)
    - Atomic bomb
    - Austria
    - Autograph
    - Banking (Box 885)
    - Books
    - Budget
    - Bureaucracy
    - Cancer
    - China
    - Civil Aeronautics Administration
    - Civil service
    - Coal
    - Commentators
    - Commissions
    - Communists
    - Compulsory military training
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
    - Contributions
    - Cooperative
    - Cost of living
    - Court-martial
    - Davis, James J.
    - Discharge
    - Economic reports, joint committee
    - Education
    - Engagements, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 886, Box 887)
    - England
    - Exports and imports
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee
    - Fair Housing Authority
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Food
    - Foreign policy
    - Germany
    - Gift
    - Greece
    - Health (Box 888)
    - House of Representatives
    - Housing
    - Immigration
    - Inflation
    - Insurance
    - Internal Revenue Service
    - Introductory letters
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitation, declined, (2 folders)
    - Japan
    - Jews
    - Justice Department
    - Labor (Box 889)
      - Legislation, (2 folders)
      - Public Welfare Committee
    - Martin, I. Jack
    - Meat
    - Memorials
    - Milk
    - Miscellaneous
    - Monetary
    - National Labor Relations Board
    - Negroes
    - Newspapers
    - Office details (Box 890)
    - Office of Price Administration
    - Ohio, state matters
    - Oil
    - Palestine
    - Political
      - Republican
    - Positions
    - Post Office Department
    - Presidency
    - Private bills
    - Propaganda
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio (Box 891)
    - Railroad
    - Railroad retirement
    - Real estate
    - Reciprocal Trade Agreement Act
    - Recommendations
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - Reorganization plan
    - Republican National Committee
    - Russia
    - Selective Service Act
    - Senate bills
    - Senate resolutions
    - Senators
    - Social Security
    - Soil conservation
    - Solid Fuels Administration
    - Speakers
    - Speech
    - State Department
    - Steel
    - Strikes
    - Subsides
    - Taft-Martin correspondence, (2 folders)
    - Taxes (Box 892)
      - Benson, Judd C.
      - Excise
      - Income
    - Teachers
    - Transfers
    - Trips
    - UNESCO
    - Unemployment compensations
    - Veterans
    - Vice presidency
    - Visitors
    - Voting
    - War
      - Investigating committee
      - Materials, disposal of
      - Powers
    - Water
    - Wheat
    - Yale
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1948 (Box 893)
    - Agriculture
    - Aid to Europe
    - Air force
    - Alaska
    - Appointments
      - Executive
    - Appropriations
    - Argentina
    - Army in Europe
    - Articles
    - Articles and statements, (1 folder) (Box 894)
    - Autograph
    - Banking
    - Biography
    - Bonds
    - Books and booklet
    - Budget
    - Christmas cards
    - Citizenship
    - Civil rights voting
    - Civil service
    - Claims
    - Coal
    - Committees
    - Communism
    - Compulsory military training
    - Condolence
    - Congratulations
    - Displaced persons
    - Economic report, joint committee
    - Education
    - Engagements, (3 folders) (Box 895)
    - Exports and imports
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission
    - Federal Reserves
    - Fisheries
    - Flood control (Box 896)
    - Foreign policy
    - Gift
    - Gold
    - Hawaii
    - Health
    - House of Representatives
    - Housing
    - Immigration
    - Inflation
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations, declined, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 897)
    - Invitations, Western trip
    - Japan (Japanese trials)
    - Jews
    - Labor legislation, (2 folders)
    - Labor and Public Welfare Commission
    - Margarine tax (Box 898)
    - Meat
    - Membership
    - Metals
    - Miscellaneous
    - National debt
    - National defense
    - Negroes
    - Newfoundland
    - Office of Price Administration
    - Ohio, state matters
    - Oil fuel
    - Mines and mining
    - Monetary
    - Palestine
    - Poll Tax
    - Political
      - General
      - Republican
    - Positions
    - Postmaster
    - Press conferences
    - Public works
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio
    - Recommendations
    - Reciprocal Trade Agreement Act
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - St. Lawrence Waterway (Box 899)
    - Salaries
    - Senate
    - Senators, correspondence
    - Speakers
    - Social security
    - State Department
    - Steel
    - Strikes
    - Tariff
    - Tax exemptions
    - Taxes
      - Excess profits
      - Income
    - Trip abroad, talks on Germany
    - United National Associations of Postal Clerks
    - United Nations
    - Veterans
    - Voting record
  - 1949 (Box 900)
    - Agriculture
    - Aid to Europe
    - Airports
    - Appointments
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Executive
    - Appropriations
    - Army, miscellaneous
    - Articles
    - Articles and statements
    - Autographs
    - Banking and Currency Committee
    - Biography, Taft
    - Books (Box 901)
    - Bowers, Thomas W.
    - Budget
    - Business, miscellaneous
    - Christmas cards
    - Cincinnati
    - Civil rights
    - Civil service
    - Civil Service Commission
    - Claims
    - Clippings
    - Columnists
    - Commerce
    - Committee
    - Commodity Credit Corp.
    - Communism
    - Compulsory military training
    - Comstock, Boyd
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
    - Contributions
    - Cooperatives
    - Course in Senate
    - Court marshall
    - Displaced persons
    - Economic Cooperation Administration (Box 902)
    - Economic report, joint committee
    - Education
    - Engagements, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 903, Box 904)
    - Exports
    - Floods
    - Foreign affairs
    - Germany
    - Gold
    - Health
    - House of Representatives (Box 905)
    - Housing
    - Hospitals
    - Immigration
    - Inflation
    - Insurance
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interior
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations, declined, (2 folders); (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 906, Box 907)
    - Japan
    - Jews
    - Klein, Julius
    - Labor, (2 folders)
      - Department
    - Legislation, (2 folders) (Box 908)
    - Lists
    - Loans
    - Marshall, John
    - Martin, I. Jack
    - Membership
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 909)
    - National Defense, Secretary of
    - National Labor Relation Board
    - Navy
    - Nuremberg trials
    - O'Berg, Blanche
    - Official business
    - Office of Price Administration
      - Rent control
    - Ohio state matters
    - Oil
    - Palestine
    - Pensions (Box 910)
    - Philippines
    - Photographs
    - Political
      - Foster, Cedric
      - General
      - Republican, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 911)
      - Taft
    - Polls
    - Positions
    - Postmasters
    - Post offices
    - Publications
    - Puerto Rico
    - Reciprocal trade Agreements
    - Recommendations
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp. (Box 912)
    - Religion
    - Reorganization plan
    - Republican National Committee
    - Reservations
    - Rural Electric Administration
    - Russia
    - St. Lawrence Waterway
    - Salaries (president)
    - School lunches
    - Senate bills
    - Senators
      - Correspondence
    - Small business
    - Social legislation
    - Social security
    - Sokolosky, George
    - Spain
    - Speech comments
    - State Departments (Box 913)
    - Steel
    - Steering committee
    - Strikes
    - Taft
      - Personal friends
    - Tariff
    - Taxes
      - Excise
    - Television
    - Unemployment compensation
    - United Nations
    - Veterans hospitals
    - Voting
    - War Department
    - Wheat
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1950 (Box 914)
    - Agriculture
    - Alaska
    - Appointment
      - Executive
    - Appropriations Committee
    - Army
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Atomic bomb
    - Autograph
    - Banking (Box 915)
    - Bonds
    - Books
    - Broadcasting
    - Budget
    - Census
    - Coffee
    - Committees
    - Commodity Credit Corp.
    - Communism
    - Condolence
    - Cooperatives
    - Congratulations, (3 folders)
    - Contributions (Box 916)
    - Displaced persons
    - District of Columbia
    - Draft
    - Economic report
    - Education
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Engagements, (3 folders)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 917)
    - Finance
    - Foreign policy
    - Gifts
    - Gold
    - Hawaii
    - House
    - House of Representatives bills
    - Immigration
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations declined, (5 folders) (Box 918)
    - Israel
    - Italy
    - Jewish (Box 919)
    - Labor
      - Legislation
      - Public Welfare Committee
    - Legislation Miscellaneous
    - Loans
    - Martin, I. Jack
    - Membership
      - Hall of Fame
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Milk (Box 920)
    - National Defense
    - Negroes
    - Ohio
    - Oil
    - Office of Price Administration